How to improve the four-sided algorithm
The four-sided optimization type of grid array algorithm has been further optimized in the new version.
First, in the previous version, we switched the grid type to the four-sided optimization option for this set of clothes.
After switching the grid type in the previous version, strange four-sided shapes will appear in some unnecessary places.
When the high-quality rendering is turned on, the preview will lead to the effect of other software.
The unreasonable placement of these grid lines will cause some grid points to be squeezed out, resulting in an unideal rough effect.
In the new version, we have a more neat and clean four-sided grid array.
There are no more unnecessary four-sided edges.
In the previous version, we switched the grid type to the four-sided optimization option for this set of clothes.
The grid line is more reasonable, so the clothes will not be in the same place as before.
Please check the comparison picture.
You can see that the four sides of the four-sided optimization are now more reasonable grid lines.
In the previous version, the grid type of four-sided optimization has been shifted to the four-sided optimization option for this set of clothes.
After the 6th generation, the grid type is now more reasonable.
You can see that there are more rooms in the four-sided optimization option for this set of clothes.
In fact, the grid line is now more reasonable for this set of clothes.
And, since it has no lower grid line, such a grid line is slightly more reasonable.
I hope you see the difference in the properties of the four-sided optimization option and the grid type of clothes.
The grid type has also been changed.